[{"answer": "Well, we've been piecing together the tragic final minutes of James Gandolfini's life.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Dan, what is the latest?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, I think it's best to say he was not the kind of blockbuster star that he was in the States here in Italy.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What has been the reaction in Rome and Italy why -- to his death?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, that's the jury that was chosen, and I do think that that's where the decision is going to be made.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "They are but just to cut to the chase here, if I am Amanda Knox, I am going to go exactly nowhere.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Because it seems that they're relying, the judge is, who called them back, on a theory that the original reason for what happened was a sex game gone wrong?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if they knew that a photo was being taken.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "And, Gloria, I was a bit struck by the fact that they're clearly very, very lovey-dovey in one those images, suggesting perhaps they're even back together, but regardless of that from a legal point of view, how sensible is it that they are seen like this together when they've just been ordered back to court?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, again, if they to extradite her perhaps but I had a case in Italy a number of years ago and frankly I don't have a whole lot of confidence in the Italian legal process.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Is there any part of the legal process that can force her to go back?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "How can you not tell me about this before?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No, it was absolutely the opposite.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Was that true?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, this watch, I saw it a long time ago on somebody's hand at a computer show and explained to me, when you see it -- when I turned my wrist, hours, minutes.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Now what does this do?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "These are old vacuum tubes called mixing tubes running on high voltage, 140 volts inside and even though it's waterproof I wouldn't take it in the bath and expect to live.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What are those?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "It's -- well, let me tell you, a lot of things about it are kind of fishy and hold it on the corners so you don't get the ink on your hands.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Is that legal tender?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "And they come in pads all of eight, right?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "All over the world I've sold them for $5 a sheet.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What would you sell the eight for that's worked before?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes, four of these bills for $5.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "So you would -- you would sell me $8 worth for $5?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Because there's so many other people around, I want to spread the joy.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Why would I not just buy this entire pad now and make an immediate 100 bucks?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm not going -- you know, there are some people that takes sides in the world and I'm always against anything government, you know, any three-letter agency or I'm always for them because I'm on the opposite side, and I'm not like that.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Are you -- are you a fan of somebody like Edward Snowden?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "The computer is going to get smarter and smarter, and more like humans.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Given the speed with which technology is advancing all the time, smart phones, computers, laptops, and so on, where are we going to be in 10 years' time?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "As far as you can tell.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Sweet little baby?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I do not know the baby's name.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Do you know the baby's name?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "No, they're not married.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "They were married?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I sure would.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Will you come back soon and do a longer interview?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes, any time, Piers.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Will you come back soon?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Because Wall Street like to -- they have this thing where you sell a news and you buy on the fear.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "So why has Wall Street gone into complete panic mode?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "No, I --", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Is there -- is there any sensible rationale for what Wall Street did today?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "YSSDAL: There's -- well, all right, your phrase.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Or is it simply taking a bit of money because they are greedy pigs?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Abby Huntsman, have you got anything to say about the global economy?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "I think it's coming, and the only question is how quickly people are going to get out of the way when it does.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Do you feel that the fact that someone like him has done this is indicative of just a sea change now coming through America quite quickly?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I'm positioning myself.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "And your positioning yourself?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Honestly nothing, just kept -- if the baby falls I just need to try to catch him.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "It's so different reading the story and then putting it on prospective when you see exactly how far the baby fell.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Are you going to stand there and try and catch that baby knowing that one false move and it could die?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "ILL: It was incredibly brave.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "I'd like to think with four kids I would do what she did but I've got to say it was an extraordinarily brave thing to do, wasn't it, Marc?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "These are the mom from the kid on the balcony?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "We now have several states in America have legalized marijuana.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Marc Lamont Hill, let me ask you one quick question.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Cameras on or cameras off?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Probably Texas and Utah just because they're weird.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "In 30 years' time will there be any state in America which still outlaws marijuana?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "I -- it really was a trail blazer, \"The Sopranos,\" wasn't it?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Take over for a while, I'll be right back.", "docId": "130620pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "If heaven exist, what would you like to hear God say when you arrive at the pearly gates?", "qSentId": 733}]